wfscorp.com 2015-09-06

# Privacy Policy | wfscorp.com

## **World Fuel Services Corporation Privacy Policy**

###   
I. Your privacy is important to us

We want you to know that when you use the World Fuel Services Corp. ("WFS") website, [www.wfscorp.com](http://www.wfscorp.com/) (the "Site"), and when you provide us with information about you, the privacy of your personally identifiable information will be respected and protected, subject to this Privacy Policy. While WFS strives to take reasonable measures to protect the privacy of its Site users, this Privacy Policy is not a contract and does not create any legal rights or obligations. Rather, the following are guidelines for protecting the information you provide to us.

### II. What information do we collect?

WFS collects and maintains personally identifiable information from those users who use the Site. Personally identifiable information includes, but is not limited to, your name, address, phone numbers, and email address. In addition, when you use our Site, certain user information and site activity data is collected. Further details on the information we collect is described below.

a.   Promotions We occasionally sponsor promotions to give users the opportunity to win various prizes. Information collected for promotions can include contact information, such as email address, and survey questions.

b.  Cookies. By using our Site, some information may automatically be collected by our web servers as you browse our Site. WFS also collects information by using technologies and methodologies that enable tracking, such as "cookies". Cookies are small bits of information that are stored on your computer by your web browser. Web beacons (also called "pixel tags") are small strings of code placed on a web page or in an email message for the purpose of transferring information. Cookies help establish a user session and allow our server to correctly provide site users with the appropriate information, advertisements and services.

c.   Domain names. In general, you can visit most parts of our web sites without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Our web servers identify the domain names and IP addresses of visitors, where applicable, but this is not captured as personally identifiable information.

d.   Children. WFS does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information online from children under the age of 13 other than when necessary to comply with federal or state regulations, or for safety and security reasons. If you learn that your child has provided us with personal information online without your knowledge, you may contact us by sending an email to [legalweb@wfscorp.com](mailto:legalweb@wfscorp.com) and ask us to delete this information from our records.

### III. How do we use your information?

We do not intend to use your personally identifiable information collected through this site or off-line in ways not described here without first providing you the opportunity to opt-out of that use.

WFS uses personal information collected in conjunction with registration or information requests on our Site. From time to time, we also use your personal information to provide you with a more effective customer experience. In order to do this, WFS may process your information or combine it with other information that we have about you or that is publicly available. In addition, WFS may share this information with third parties for the purpose of providing you with services, information or promotional opportunities that may be of interest to you. We require strict contractual obligations from these third parties to ensure safeguards for the privacy and security of the information which are at least as restrictive as this Privacy Policy in handling your information.

a.   Emails. We use email addresses to deliver information relevant to our users and customers, such as product specials, surveys, account information, notification services, and for administrative reasons. We hope you will find these updates and communications interesting and informative. Of course, if you would rather not receive this information, you may opt-out of receiving such emails as described below

b.   Online surveys and promotions. We value the opinions of our customers and want to improve your experience and our service offerings; therefore, from time to time, we will conduct research surveys. We may also contract with third parties to perform the research, but the use of the customer data by that third party is limited solely to that survey initiative and is protected by a confidentiality agreement. Generally, unless otherwise stated in the promotion or survey, contact information collected for promotions is used to notify promotion winners, and survey information and results are used to develop improved promotions and other service enhancements.

c.  Cookies. Cookies help establish a user session and allow our server to correctly provide site users with the appropriate information, advertisements and services. We also use cookies to ensure you obtain the information you request and to authenticate your authority to access the Site. We also use cookies and web beacons to track the usage of our Site in order to improve the site according to our customers’ needs.

WFS may enter into agreements with third party companies to serve advertisements and information to Site users. WFS may use its cookies and web beacons when working with these companies to provide them information regarding use of the Site or to serve you advertisements when you visit our Site. These companies may use the non-personally identifiable information about your visit to make available goods and services of interest to you.

If, at any time, you do not want your non-personally identifiable information to be used to provide you with more relevant information, advertisements, or services available from WFS, you can change the settings on your Internet browser to reject cookies and this will also disable our web beacons. Please consult your chosen Internet browser for instructions on how to change your cookie handling settings.

d.   Domain names. Information regarding domain names is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the Site, pages viewed and similar Site usage information in order to know how to improve the Site’s content.

e.   Children. No information we collect from children known to be under the age of 13 is used for any marketing or promotional purposes whatsoever, by either us, our affiliates, or our third party sponsors. We use the information collected about children known to be under 13 only to provide services. We will give out personal information about children if required by law, for example, to comply with a court order or subpoena or to protect the safety and security of visitors and our Site.

f.   Law Enforcement / Legal processes / Other uses. WFS may disclose personal information if required to do so by law, court order, subpoena or other legal process, as requested by a governmental or law enforcement authority, or when we believe in good faith that it is in the interests of aviation security or that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable.

### V.How is the information collected online protected?

WFS maintains strict physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect personal information and regularly reviews its security standards and procedures to protect against unauthorized access to personal information. Although WFS takes reasonable steps to safeguard and to prevent unauthorized access to your private information, it cannot be responsible for the acts of those who gain unauthorized access, and WFS makes no warranty, express, implied, or otherwise, that we will prevent unauthorized access to your private information.

### VI.How can you opt out?

If you do not want WFS to use or share your personal information for the purpose of sending you email marketing or promotional materials, please send an email to [legalweb@wfscorp.com](mailto:legalweb@wfscorp.com) and request that no further communications be sent to you. In addition, emails sent to you will also contain a message on how to opt out of that type of communication in the future. Regardless of your opt-out preferences, we reserve the right to send you emails or other electronic messages for administrative purposes.

### VII. Other sites

This Privacy Policy, to the extent it covers Internet use, covers only the Site and does not cover any other site, including those that may related or linked to this Site. While we make every effort to protect your information on our Site, we do not control the policies of other sites (including those we may link to). We have no control over other sites’ privacy policies or use of any personal information you or others may share with them. Please do not assume that our Privacy Policy covers those other sites.

### VIII. Protect your personal information

In order to protect your privacy and WFS’ proprietary databases and systems, we recommend that you not share any of your personally identifiable information with us directly and/or with any third-party information aggregators that would allow them access to your sensitive information.

### IX. How can you contact us?

If you have comments or questions about this Privacy Policy, please email us at [legalweb@wfscorp.com](mailto:legalweb@wfscorp.com) . Please reference this Privacy Policy in those communications.

### X. Legal effect and changes to the policy

As indicated, this Privacy Policy is not a contract nor does it otherwise create any legal rights or obligations. Rather, this Privacy Policy merely reflects guidelines setting forth WFS’ intended business practices. However, by using the Site, and/or by providing personal information to WFS online or off-line, you consent to the collection and use of such information by WFS, its affiliates, partners, contractors and permitted agents consistent with applicable laws. Also, WFS, in its discretion, may amend, interpret, modify, or withdraw any portion of this Privacy Policy and related business practices at any time by posting updated text on this site, and your continued use constitutes your consent to those changes. A version of this Privacy Policy has been effective since September 2010. Thank you for taking the time to read this Privacy Policy.
